We meet again.
Do you feel like
I look like an evil teddy bear today?
Back here again.
Such a familiar scene.
Good morning, students.
Today is our second exam day.
Over the past few days,
you've each chosen your own partner.
But have you
really gotten to know each other?
Now it's time to find out.
Two pairs of partners will stand on a sheet of white paper.
The other two pairs will take turns asking questions about each other.
Each partner must answer simultaneously,
after a three-two-one countdown.
If you answer wrong,
or not at the same time,
you must fold the paper under your feet once.
Once any body part touches the ground,
that pair is eliminated.
The team that answers the most questions correctly
gets to choose the order of assessment first.
Chemistry?
We have no chemistry at all.
Are we the ones with the best chemistry?
I have no idea.
Understood.
Okay.
Both pairs, step onto the paper.
We'll be asking the questions.
Take a look.
You're done for.
Fifteen questions.
You won't answer a single one right.
I feel it too.
Good luck.
The questions won't be easy.
They're tough.
They'll really test your chemistry.
He's putting pressure on you.
He's pressuring you.
What do we do now?
What do we do?
Just do it.
You can beg us first.
First question.
What does Bai Guanyu think is
Jiang Xiaomeng's greatest strength?
Three, two, one.
Handsome.
Sincere.
That three-two-one was way too fast.
Too fast.
You two have no chemistry at all.
That doesn't count.
Of course it counts.
Fold it in half first.
We already counted down.
There was already a timer.
Wait, you're playing too.
Watch how we do it.
I think this one is pretty easy.
What's going on?
Now it's our turn.
The first question is...
Come on.
Look at me.
What kind of person does Sun Mingyang dislike
being friends with the most?
Three.
Two.
One.
'Pretentious'.
Someone like me.
Do you two even have any chemistry?
Why did you answer 'someone like me'?
I...
If you answer 'someone like me, ' what am I supposed to say?
Someone like you.
Came here just to show off.
Fold.
Go ahead and fold.
Start folding.
Fold.
You two have zero chemistry.
Hopeless.
Totally hopeless.
Alright.
Our side starts now.
Which does Jiang Xiaomeng believe in more,
that hearts connect without words,
or that you should always speak your mind?
Three.
Two.
One.
Speak your mind.
Telepathy.
You two really are
on the same wavelength.
Aren't we already on the same wavelength?
Fold it quickly.
If we fold it this way,
won't we have more spots to stand on?
I think this way is better.
What are you two hesitating about?
Why so ambiguous?
Why is it so ambiguous?
Alright.
I'm going to be ambiguous now.
Question two,
how many times a day does Sun Mingyang look in the mirror?
Three.
Two, one.
Countless times.
Ten times.
Fold.
It's definitely countless times.
Sun Mingyang.
This is Sun Mingyang we're talking about.
His suitcase is full of magic mirrors.
Still, Zhang Ziyu doesn't know you well enough.
We're done for.
It's like being on a lonely island.
Right.
Please, little brothers.
Please, Bro Zhou.
You know, today the two of us,
won't even give you a chance for revenge.
What do Jiang Xiaomeng do when you can't sleep?
Three, two, one.
Listen to bedtime.
Play video games.
Stories.
One listens to stories.
One plays video games.
That's so telepathic.
It's just that you two have zero chemistry.
Can we have a little chemistry, please?
I don't want to stand on the same blank paper as you.
Next question is
now,
what's the one phrase you most want to say to each other?
Just one word.
Three, two, one.
Get lost.
At a moment like this, we're actually perfectly in sync.
The most in-sync partners.
We went easy on you this round.
Right.
Seeing how out of sync you two are,
we really couldn't bear to mess with you.
We're way too in sync.
They're about to be eliminated.
What's Bai Guanyu's most sensitive body part?
Three, two, one.
Chest.
Heart.
The heart?
Have you no shame?
This one...
They've already been eliminated.
Their feet are so small.
That's not even as big as one of Jiang Xiaomeng's feet.
You're stepping on me.
You're stepping on my foot.
So ambiguous.
Come on.
Feel each other's warmth.
Your foot is clearly outside, isn't it?
It's not fair, my feet are a bigger size.
Look,
this.
Look at this heel.
What's wrong with your heel?
Tiptoe up.
Tiptoe.
Get up on your toes.
Is this okay?
I guess that works.
I'll count it.
Zhang Ziyu thinks,
who's the best-looking among the eight?
Three, two, one.
Sun Mingyang.
I'd never admit that.
You? The best-looking of the group?
What's wrong with me being the best-looking?
What's wrong with that?
Come on.
Let's take a vote.
All seven of you vote.
No use.
It's about the chemistry between us two.
Bai Guanyu and Jiang Xiaomeng
decide who's more handsome.
Bai Guanyu.
Finally, some chemistry.
What does Sun Mingyang most want to be praised for?
Being handsome.
Even though I really don't want to answer that,
what's there not to want to answer?
Use one adjective to describe your relationship.
Best friends.
Come on, fold it.
We can't fold them all.
You two figure it out yourselves.
Work it out yourselves.
One, two.
Alright,
Just tell me already.
What's Sun Mingyang's most hated instrument?
Guitar.
Because I play guitar.
You two need to think of something to make them fold the paper.
They're way too in sync.
What can we do?
We already picked the hardest questions.
We're seriously on the same wavelength right now.
Does Jiang Xiaomeng think Bai Guanyu
is more like a kitten or a puppy?
Kitten.
Puppy.
Eliminated.
It's fine.
No big deal.
Next up,
the final question
will Sun Mingyang choose to run ten kilometers,
or publicly post Zhang Ziyu's embarrassing photos?
Run ten kilometers.
Well, congrats to Sun Mingyang and Zhang Ziyu
for answering five questions.
Quite good.
Alright.
Come on.
I'll go.
I'm going to make them
get every single question wrong.
Just watch.
Today's game,
I have to win them all.
Remember what I said,
I'll take first place in every game.
Let me show you what real chemistry is.
We show no mercy to our rivals.
Ask all the hard ones,
who cares, let's just go.
This one's definitely...
First question.
Out of the eight people,
who does Wang Ruijian least like to cling to?
Three.
Two.
One.
Ma Weixian.
Alright.
Fold.
My bad.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you answer?
He wouldn't even answer me.
What's that?
Sorry.
Actually, he just doesn't want to get close to you.
Let them have one question first.
Pros don't win the first round.
Let's go with this one.
If Ma Weixian were a food,
what would he be?
This one's really hard.
Three.
Two.
One.
Hamburger.
See, you answered too slow.
Fold it.
This really smells.
Let's do this.
The thing Chen Zhixuan says most to Wang Ruijian is...
Get lost.
That's so versatile.
I've noticed there's already a template, right?
Yeah.
If this were a fairy tale world,
which story's protagonist
would Zhou Guorui think he is?
Three.
Two.
One.
Doraemon.
Alright.
Pass.
Too slow, too slow.
You ask them.
There's no way they'd get it right.
If you think of the other person as a temperature,
how many degrees would they be?
Fifty degrees.
Fifty.
Three hundred sixty degrees.
Honestly, even I could answer that one.
This is way too hard.
Too hard.
All I can say is, I'm sorry.
If for the rest of your life,
you could only eat food of one color,
what color would Zhou Guorui choose?
Red.
Hamburger.
I think this one's hard.
That works.
No problem.
If Chen Zhixuan had to bring one member to a deserted island,
who would it be?
Wang Ruijian.
Such great chemistry.
Come on, plug your ears.
Okay, done.
Ears plugged.
If
Ma Weixian were a food.
What would he be?
Hamburger.
Too slow.
The exact same question, asked twice,
and you still got it wrong?
Right.
They made it easy on purpose.
Okay?
Where's the chemistry we promised?
Where's our chemistry?
Show some chemistry.
I want to stuff my foot in your mouth right now.
Interesting.
Wang Ruijian,
when he sleeps, does he wear boxers,
or briefs?
Answer.
Briefs.
A.
Is A briefs or boxers?
Briefs.
Same answer.
He wears briefs.
Don't most boys wear boxers?
Right, around me,
hardly anyone wears briefs.
Because I've seen him wear them.
That secret's not for everyone to know.
Everyone knows.
Can you give us a multiple-choice question?
Sure.
Come on, take a guess.
Good luck, bro.
Which virtual character would Ma Weixian want to be friends with?
Three.
Two.
One.
Zhou Guorui.
Fictional.
Am I a virtual character?
You're carrying a digital human.
AI human.
Just fold it.
We haven't gotten a single question right, have we?
Yep.
Wang Ruijian is taking a shower.
Suddenly the power goes out.
Does Wang Ruijian go out covering his face,
or covering his body?
His face.
They seem to be on question four.
We're on five.
They're about to catch up with us.
Let's trip them up a bit.
We're the ones with the best chemistry.
Come on.
I'll carry you, bro.
Here.
Okay.
Come on.
Ask quickly!
You did that on purpose.
How many abs does Ma Weixian have?
Six.
Eight.
He said eight.
You said eight.
You got an eight-pack?
No.
Aren't abs always eight-pack?
One.
There's no such thing as eight. Only one.
Out.
Bro, we're the real 'plastic' friendship.
Congratulations to Ma Weixian and Zhou Guorui
for getting zero questions right.
I actually thought we could get every one right.
Yeah.
We were just a tiny bit off.
Wang Ruijian falls on the road,
and accidentally pulls down Chen Zhixuan's pants,
so does Chen Zhixuan pull up his pants first,
or help Wang Ruijian first?
Pull up your pants.
We won!
We're about to win!
We can't do multiple choice questions anymore. Seriously.
There's nothing left except multiple choice.
You can come up with your own question.
I come up with it myself?
If so, they couldn't answer a single question.
Here we go.
What is Wang Ruijian's favorite color?
Three, two, one.
Blue!
One more question.
What is Chen Zhixuan's real height?
Three, two, one.
181 centimeters.
They must have
discussed it last night, right?
What is Wang Ruijian's real height?
Three, two, one.
Shut up!
We can't say that.
Ruijian's real height
can't be known by others.
You two really have great chemistry.
I hereby announce,
you are our most in-sync pair.
Of course we are.
Alright.
Congratulations to Wang Ruijian and Chen Zhixuan
for winning first place.
You get to choose
our performance order.
Let's go second.
Okay, up to you.
Second.
Hello, teacher.
What was our first assessment?
It was me.
Me.
And now we're about to start the second exam.
What do you think the second exam should be about?
You.
Right,
the topic of our second assessment,
is "you".
This time, you need to temporarily set yourselves aside,
and step into your partner's world.
Through observation and understanding,
present the other person as you see them.
This is so hard.
Yeah, it's pretty tough.
Have you thought of anything?
I've got a rough outline.
Something's taking shape.
So, in this next stage,
you'll each be writing a character biography of each other.
Writing this stuff?
How am I supposed to write this?
Can someone write it for me?
A character biography.
I've never seen one, no idea how to write it.
Do you have any ideas?
Let me think.
For the character biography...
give me a second.
What are Guorui's traits?
So can it be written in first person?
Yeah, like, "My name is Zhang Ziyu."
Then let's do that.
Let's just write it in first person.
I think we can
keep it simple like this.
I'm writing his name.
My name is Ma Weixian.
Take a good look at this person.
I don't even need to look, bro.
The picture's already in my head.
This is the portrait I drew for Wang Ruijian.
Big eyes,
and a mouth that's always smiling.
His big eyes are his signature.
I think it's pretty cute,
even though it's a bit ugly.
I think writing a character biography means,
write the character Ruijian
from a first-person perspective.
So I think of
his usual,
behaviors and stories.
For example, he's also
a narcissistic kid.
Out of the eight of us, who do you think is the most handsome?
Me.
But
he's actually pretty vulnerable and sensitive too.
And he's also
a kid who sets high standards for himself.
Very independent and clear-headed.
Someone with clear goals of his own.
Let me see what else I can write.
Is he a pig or something?
He's always asking me to get late-night snacks with him.
He has four meals a day,
which I really can't understand.
He roasts me.
He'd definitely say I'm super hard to imitate.
He thinks I have no distinctive traits.
I'm writing this much about him,
if he only writes me one line,
I'm gonna get mad later.
I really will get mad.
I'd just punch him.
With others, he mostly shows
his sunny, cheerful side.
But actually you find he's also
a boy who feels pretty insecure, and rather fragile.
Actually, he's good at using his kindness,
and cheerfulness to package himself.
Let's see whose room this is.
You're done writing?
Of course.
Is there really that little to say about me?
I heard from my PD,
that someone got a name wrong.
Who was it?
Not me.
It's not that they got it wrong,
he straight-up couldn't remember your name.
Who was it?
I don't know.
But that 'Zhi' in his name is...
How do you write the 'Ming' in Sun Mingyang?
Me?
It wasn't me.
I wrote about you very seriously.
I've been imagining what you're like.
You are...
You finished writing it in such a short time?
Mine is prose.
Do you know what prose is?
He's gone.
Looking at his face.
I would draw from what we've been through,
from the first time we met,
including his personality,
and the feelings it gave me.
I can really feel his rebelliousness and wildness.
I'll start
from the first time he told us
about his own childhood stories,
I've been building up his life bit by bit.
He must have gone to primary school,
high school, middle school.
What setbacks would he have faced?
What kind of stories would there be?
You wrote that much?
Got emotional writing it?
I got emotional writing it.
It just flowed.
Sun Mingyang will be moved to death.
No way.
I didn't write a single nice thing about him.
Zhang Ziyu is
the classic "tough outside, gentle inside" type.
And then,
he doesn't like troubling others,
and doesn't really need other people's help,
and doesn't really depend on others either.
He probably can't do what I do, bringing the completely real me,
straight onto the stage.
Sharing that state with everyone.
He probably still needs
a so-called shell,
a mask.
Wearing a mask and shell every day
is actually pretty exhausting.
I feel like he's the kind of person who secretly wipes away tears.
But I'm not sure,
because I've never seen it.
After he hears my biography of him,
he should be so moved that
he cried his eyes out.
He must have.
All I can say is that compared to him,
I understand him even better now.
I am now another Sun Mingyang
in this world.
What are Guorui's traits, then?
Chen Zhixuan, what do you think?
My impression of Guorui so far...
I think he has a really good quality,
he has a very relaxed mindset.
I think, actually that kind of mindset is great.
It helps you
focus better on the task at hand.
It lets me
relieve a lot of pressure.
You draw so well!
Isn't that his standard smile?
Because I really think he's
someone who can't be put into words.
You know?
That's it.
He is quirk and interesting... beyond imagination.
So might as well just draw a picture.
Look at my fighter jet.
A fighter jet for Guorui.
I've already written yours.
I think.
I think it's great.
I think it's really well written.
Come on, my dear deskmate.
Let me take a look.
Let me see what kind of person I am.
Do you think it's okay?
I just want to ask.
If it's okay, I'll leave.
I think...
I came over to get some inspiration from you.
Now you're judging me?
It's fine.
So it's fine, right?
What do you think of what I wrote?
I think you wrote it really well.
I'm heading back.
I don't think it was hard at all,
because our personalities are a bit alike.
Carefree and easygoing.
Happy and cheerful.
I just feel like I'm just like him.
I'm always lying like this, and he lies like this too.
Exactly the same.
Completely identical.
It's that feeling of
finding your own real brother.
I want to complete this very seriously
a character biography.
Because about Bai Guanyu,
I feel like I
have so, so many things I want to say.
Of course, I wrote it from
the perspective that I'm Bai Guanyu.
So, I worked backwards
to figure out what he might be like.
I really long for a good friend.
I really long to be chosen.
I really long
to be noticed.
I think to understand someone,
you have to get close to them.
So,
I wrote everything I learned about him
into a character biography.
It's also
a story.
When I truly calmed down,
and spent those 30 minutes describing him,
I discovered
that a lot of things
weren't what he told me.
They just suddenly
burst into my mind.
My own idea of what kind of person he might be.
I think you should be more confident.
From your eyes,
I saw a lot of uncertainty.
It's okay.
I want to get to know you.
I think maybe
a lot of the time he needs to be
heard.
He needs to be recognized.
I'd say maybe
70 or 80 percent.
60 or 70.
Around 60 or 70 percent.
I think that's about right.
Like 60 percent.
60 or 70 percent.
Maybe 60 percent.
90 percent likely.
30, 20 percent.
Less than 10 percent.
I'd say it's hard to tell.
Uh-oh.
He chased her downstairs. It's fine.
This doesn't look good.
How's he popping it so fast?
Totally in sync.
Even a 50/50 guess was wrong.
Get lost!
Cool!
Guitar.
Hamburger.
Too slow.
Can we talk?
What's there to talk about?
Don't give up.
What?